2;Básico;Question words;Choose the best question for the following answer: "Yesterday.";When did you arrive?;What did you do?;When will you finish it?;Where did you arrive?
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "What __________ he do for a living? He is an architect.";does;has;is;do
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative to complete the question. "Where _______________ find a pen?";can I find;don't I;I can't find;is
2;Básico;Question words;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "When __________ your birthday?";is;does;are;will
2;Básico;Question words;|Choose the incorrect alternative: 
Susan: "How does he drive?"
Bart: "__________."|;Never;Fast;Carefully;Well
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the question: 
James: " __________ is the meeting room?"
Michelle: "Downstairs."|;Where;When;What;Why
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "I'm organizing a party. __________ can came?";Who;When;Why;What
2;Básico;Question words;Match the question to the answer: "Because I had too much to do.";"Why did you go to work on Saturday?";"When did you go to work?";"What are you doing here?";"Why did you watch this movie?"
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "What time __________ the bus __________?";does/leave;does/leaves;do/leaves;do/leave
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the incorrect alternative: "Where are you __________ ?";parents;going;staying;now
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the question: 
Nicolas: "__________ does he work?" 
Robert: "He works downtown."|;Where;When;What;Who
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the best alternative: "I like your bag. __________ did you buy it?";Where;What;Who;What's
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "Who __________ in that apartment?";lives;live;living;does live
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "Excuse me, __________ the subway station, please?";where is;is where;who is;when is
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "_______________ your mother's name?;What is;How is;Who is;Is what
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ many letters are there in your name?";How;What;Which;Do
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "_______________ the president of your country?";Who is;How is;When is;Who are
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ country is your father from?";What;Where;Who;When
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ my pen? I need to sign this document.";Where is;Is where;When is;How is
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ much does it cost to fly to Japan?";How;What;Which;Who
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the best alternative: "What kind of car _______________?";does she have;she has;is she having;we have
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ do your parents do?";What;Who;When;Which
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the question:
Sandra: "_______________ the last time you traveled abroad?"
Chris: "It was 5 years ago."|;When was;When is;Where was;What
2;Básico;Question words;|Choose the correct alternative:
Aimee: "__________ is the Louvre?"
Peter: "It is a museum."|;What;When;How;Which
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the question:
John: "__________ is the capital of France?"
Tom: "It is Paris."|;What;Where;When;How
2;Básico;Question words;|Choose the correct alternative:
Ann: "__________ is Tom Cruise?"
Paula: "He is an actor."|;Who;What;Where;When
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the question:
Mick: "__________ is Carnival in Rio de Janeiro?"
Ted: "It is usually in February." |;When;What;Where;How
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ does it cost to fly to Buenos Aires?";How much;How many;Where;How
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ apples do we have to buy?";How many;When;Where;How much
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ is the Sahara desert?";Where;When;How many;Whose
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the dialogue:
Kate: "__________ are the Andes Mountains?"
John: "They are in South America."|;Where;When;How;Which
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ dress do you prefer? The white one or the black one?";Which;Where;How;When
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the dialogue:
Mark: "__________ is the New York Times?"
Peter: "It is an American newspaper."|;What;Where;Which;How much
2;Básico;Question words;Match the question to the answer: "Because I woke up too early.";"Why are you so tired?";"Why don't you go to bed?";"Where is your office?";"What time do you wake up?"
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the question:
Suzy: "Why __________ open the window?"
Carl: "Because it's cold."|;don't you;do you;you don't;can you
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the question:
Sarah: "When __________ your parents __________ to Europe?"
Jane: "Last January."|;did/travel;did/traveled;do/travel;does/travel
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "_______________ going tomorrow? To the city center?";Where are you;Where you are ;When are you ;When you are
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ time does the movie __________?";What/start;What/starts;When/start;When/starts
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ is your favorite TV show about?";What;Which;How;Why
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ is more dangerous: hiking in Canada or surfing in Australia?";What;Where;Who;How
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ do you think that man is waiting for? His wife?";Who;What;Where;When
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ is his favorite author?";Who;When;Whose;Why
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ does Tom live?";Where;Who;What;Which
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ do you prefer: lamb or chicken?";Which;Who;Where;Whose
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ do you usually spend your holidays?";Where;Who;Which;Whose
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the dialogue: 
Tim: "__________ keys are these?"
Ann: "They are my keys." |;Whose;Where;Who;Which
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the dialogue: 
John: "_______________ is the movie?"
Tessa: "It's about 2 hours long." |;How long;What;Which;Where
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ do you usually do on weekends?" ;What;Where;When;Which
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ do you usually arrive from work?" ;What time;How long;What;How often
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ do you go to the movies?" ;How often;How long;What;Whose
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ is the car?" ;Where;Who;When;Why
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ don't you come with us?" ;Why;What;When;Which
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ do you go to school every day?" ;How;Which;How often;Who
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ is the bus fare where you live?" ;How much;How long;Where;Whose
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ are the tickets to the concert?" ;How much;How long;When;How often
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ people are there in Chicago?" ;How many;How long;How often;How much
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ is Tom's grandmother?" ;How old;How many;How often;How much
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ does your son visit you?" ;How often;What;Which;How many
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ is New York from Chicago?";How far;How often;How;Which
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ does it take from here to Boston?";How long;How far;How often;How
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ is this in your bag? It is a pencil." ;What;Which;Where;When
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ music do you listen to?" ;What kind of;How long;How many;Which
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ do you pick up the children at school?" ;What time;How long;How many;What
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ is your 11th wedding anniversary?";When;What;Which;How many
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ are you going after work?" ;Where;When;What;Which
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ is that girl in the blue dress?" ;Who;Which;How long;When
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ do you usually have lunch with?";Who;Whose;How;What
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ do you normally spend your holidays with?";Who;Whose;How;Where
2;Básico;Question words;|Complete the dialogue:
Paul: "__________ jacket is this?"
Tina: "It's Janet's."|;Whose;Who;Where;When
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ made the donation?";Who;Whose;Which;What
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ broke my guitar?";Who;Whose;Which;When
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ often do you have French classes?";How;Which;What;Do
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ much does this jacket cost?";How;What;Which;How many
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ do you make these delicious cookies? Can you give me the recipe?";How;What;How many;Which
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ do you take to the airport by bus?";How long;How;When;Where
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ do you pay to get your hair cut?";How much;How many;Which;How long
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ students are there in your class?";How many;How much;How long;How far
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ is your nephew? __________ is his birthday?";How old/When;When/How old;Who/How old;How old/Who
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ do you take martial arts classes?";How often;What;How much;How many
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ do you usually have for dinner?";What;Where;When;Whose
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ books do you like reading?";What kind of;How;Where;When
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ do you usually go to bed?";What time;What kind of;Which;How long
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ does you father usually get home?";What time;How long;How many;What kind of
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ is your next business meeting?";When;How many;Whose;Who
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "There is a cat in our front yard. __________ is it?";Whose;When;How many;What kind of
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ does Tom usually get home from school?";How;Who;What;Which
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ do you pay for rent every month?";How much;How many;How far;How long
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ people are coming to the party next Saturday?";How many;How much;How long;Who
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ is your dog?";How old;When;How often;How many
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ does Ted take guitar lessons?";How often;What;Which;What kind of
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ are you crying? Don't cry. It's going to be all right.";Why;What;Which;How many
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ are you so nervous? Just relax and take a deep breath.";Why;What;Which;How many
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ does it take to fly from New York to Chicago?";How long;How ;How often;How many
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ do you do every day after dinner?";What;How;Which;When
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ sport do you do?";What kind of;How;How long;How often
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ does Jennifer finish work every day?";What time;What;What kind of;Which
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ is Jenn's 30th birthday?";When;How many;What kind of;Whose
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ is your favorite place to eat in New York?";Where;When;What kind of;Who
2;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ is your favorite? Thai or Mexican food?";Which;Where;When;What kind of
2;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "There is a pair of sunglasses on the table. __________ is it?";Whose;When;What;What kind of
